{
  "quizzes": [
    {
        "titel": "quiz_1",
        "questions": [
            {
                "question":"1. what is the name of the 1 mana, mana rock that is a stable in commander?",
                "answers": {
                    "a": "Sol ring",
                    "b": "Arcane Signet",
                    "c": "Commander's Sphere",
                    "d": "Mana Crypt"
        
                },
                "correctAnswer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question":"2. What is the name of the 4 angel sisters of innistrad?",
                "answers": {
                    "a": "Akroma, Atraxa, Aurelia and Avacyn",
                    "b": "Gisela, Bruna, Sigarda and Avacyn",
                    "c": "Gisela, Bruna, Sigarda and Liesa",
                    "d": "Bruna, Anya, Lyra and Giada"
        
                },
                "correctAnswer": "b"
            },
            {
                "question":"3. What are the colors of the Boros Legion?",
                "answers": {
                    "a": "Black and Green",
                    "b": "Red and white",
                    "c": "Green and blue",
                    "d": "Blue and white"
                },
                "correctAnswer": "b"
            },
            {
                "question":"4. What is the name of the plane where the eldrazi were sealed away originally?",
                "answers": {
                    "a": "Innistrad",
                    "b": "Ravnica",
                    "c": "Amonkhet",
                    "d": "Zendikar"
        
                },
                "correctAnswer": "d"
            },
            {
                "question":"5. how where the shards of alara formed?",
                "answers": {
                    "a": "A planeswalker draining alara of its mana.",
                    "b": "The eldrazi feeding off the alara,s mana",
                    "c": "A massive war that ruptured the plane.",
                    "d": "The people displeasing the gods."
                },
                "correctAnswer": "a"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "titel": "quiz_2",
        "questions": [
            {
                "question":"1. what is the name of the 1 mana, mana rock that is a stable in commander?",
                "answers": {
                    "a": "Sol ring",
                    "b": "Arcane Signet",
                    "c": "Commander's Sphere",
                    "d": "Mana Crypt"
        
                },
                "correctAnswer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question":"2. What is the name of the 4 angel sisters of innistrad?",
                "answers": {
                    "a": "Akroma, Atraxa, Aurelia and Avacyn",
                    "b": "Gisela, Bruna, Sigarda and Avacyn",
                    "c": "Gisela, Bruna, Sigarda and Liesa",
                    "d": "Bruna, Anya, Lyra and Giada"
        
                },
                "correctAnswer": "b"
            },
            {
                "question":"3. What are the colors of the Boros Legion?",
                "answers": {
                    "a": "Black and Green",
                    "b": "Red and white",
                    "c": "Green and blue",
                    "d": "Blue and white"
                },
                "correctAnswer": "b"
            },
            {
                "question":"4. What is the name of the plane where the eldrazi were sealed away originally?",
                "answers": {
                    "a": "Innistrad",
                    "b": "Ravnica",
                    "c": "Amonkhet",
                    "d": "Zendikar"
        
                },
                "correctAnswer": "d"
            },
            {
                "question":"5. how where the shards of alara formed?",
                "answers": {
                    "a": "A planeswalker draining alara of its mana.",
                    "b": "The eldrazi feeding off the alara,s mana",
                    "c": "A massive war that ruptured the plane.",
                    "d": "The people displeasing the gods."
                },
                "correctAnswer": "a"
            }
        ]
    }

  ]
}